<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;kbfields&quot; and file.name=&quot;kmknowledgebase&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=&quot;kmknowledgebase.idol.g&quot; and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="kbfields - kmknowledgebase -  - kmknowledgebase.idol.g - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">kbfields</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">kmknowledgebase</file.name>
    <format.name type="string">kmknowledgebase.idol.g</format.name>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">Define the field mapping for the library.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">Field Name: Specifies the field name in the Service Manager table included in the index.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Alias: Specifies the name that the field is to be indexed as. You can make use of the Alias field to have a single common field name for searching and for the hitlist. For example, you may wish to alias different fields from different tables as "Title" so that they can be searched by using Advanced Search. Fields can have more than one alias. Separate these fields with a semicolon. An alias can be the same name as the field name. If the alias name includes ".", the system converts the period to an underscore when indexed.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Type: Indicates whether the field is a plain text string, a rich text string, or a date type. The indexer ignores HTML markup in rich text strings and indexes plain text strings completely. Rich text? This value is for the legacy SOLR search. Reference: some entity has the reference relationship. It applies the reference field to display the information that is meaningful to the user.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Hitlist: Defines what fields are available on the search hitlist. Fields marked as "true" in the hitlist column are available to be included on a search hitlist. The information for these field is displayed at the bottom of the search result.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Index weight: Defines the sequence of the search results which are displayed on the search hitlist. You can assign different index weight to adjust the display sequence. If the sort value of a field is assigned as level 4, the search results of this field is displayed at the top of the list. No index means that this field is not used for search.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Match: By setting the field in this column to "true," the system indexes the field's content as an advanced search filter for Smart Search in this knowledgebase. The search engine searches this individual field with the Advanced Search filter. For example, if you set the Category field as true, this field is used as an advanced search filter.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Sort: Defines the sequence of the search results which are displayed on the search hitlist. If you set multiple fields as hitlist, you can decide the display sequence by assigning different sort values for these fields. If the sort value of a field is assigned as 1, the search results of this field is displayed at the top of the list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Data cleasing: Used to remove a field from the table before indexing.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">07/26/16 21:18:24</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">pengfei</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">9</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">07/26/16 21:18:24</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">true</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
