<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;calc&quot; and file.name=&quot;report&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="calc - report -  -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">calc</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">report</file.name>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">The type of calculation to perform using the value of the field or variable defined in Field/Variable Names to Total.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Service Manager performs the indicated calculation for every detail record processed by the report regardless of whether the detail form is printed.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">This field works in conjunction with the Field/Variable Names To Total field and the Variable Names On Format field.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If you specify a variable for the Field/Variable Names To Total field, the value contained in that variable when each detail record is printed (or would have been printed if you had specified Detail in the Summary/Detail field) is accumulated in the variable specified in the Variable Names On Format field.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">OPTIONS</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">AVG: If selected (set to true), accumulates the values of a specified field for each detail record extracted by the Primary File Query or Stacked Queries, and the total number of detail records read that produced the accumulated total.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When Service Manager detects a break, it divides the accumulated total by the total number of records and stores the result in the variable defined in the Variable Names On Format field. The break also causes the subtotals form to print, which resets the variable used to accumulate the totals and the total number of records to zero.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">MIN: If selected (set to true), examines the value of a specified field in each detail records and retain the lowest value encountered.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When Service Manager detects a break, it stores the lowest value in the variable defined in the Variable Names On Format field. The break also causes the subtotals form to print, which resets the variable used to accumulate the totals and the total number of records to zero.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">MAX: If selected (set to true), examines the value of a specified field in each detail record and retain the highest value encountered.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When Service Manager detects a break, it stores the highest value in the variable defined in the Variable Names On Format field. The break also causes the subtotals form to print, which resets the variable used to accumulate the totals and the total number of records to zero.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">SUM: If selected (set to true), accumulates the values of a specified field for each detail record extracted by the Primary File Query or Stacked Queries.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When Service Manager detects a break, it stores the accumulated total in the variable defined in the Variable Names On Format field. The break also causes the subtotals form to print, which resets the variable used to accumulate the totals and the total number of records to zero.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:19</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:29</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
