<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;encrypt&quot; and file.name=&quot;datadict&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="encrypt - datadict -  -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">encrypt</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">datadict</file.name>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">If selected (set to true), encrypts data a the field level within the database.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Set the field to false (clear the checkbox) to revert the data back to its un-encrypted state.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Data is encrypted on a field-by-field basis.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">If you have encrypted any field in your database, make sure that you store the KEY value defined in the sc.ini file in a safe place. Without the correct KEY value, you will not be able to decrypt.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When the Data Policy for a table changes, the system checks to see if the encryption status has changed. If the status has changed from False to True then each record in the file is read, the field is encrypted, and the data written back to the file. If the status has changed from True to False then each record in the file is read, the field is decrypted, and the data written back to the file. The entire process takes as long as it takes to read and update each record in the file, and a performance loss may result.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">You can set the KEY value used to encrypt data on your system with the encryptionkey parameter in the sc.ini file. This field must be exactly 8 bytes in length.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If you change the KEY value, then every field in every file must be checked and re-encrypted, if necessary. Changing the KEY value will result in a significant performance hit to the system while re-encryption is taking place. Make sure you allow for this when changing the encryption key.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:34</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:47</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
