<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;Doc mgmt analysis reports&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="Doc mgmt analysis reports -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">Doc mgmt analysis reports</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">This is the Incident Analysis Reporting menu.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Use this menu to run various Incident Analysis reports.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">The menu only displays reports you have the authorization to run.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">OPTIONS</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F1 - Alert Status Report: Runs the Alert Status report using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "asr".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F2 - Assignment Group Report: Runs the document by assignment group report using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "agr".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F3 - Incident Management Menu: Returns you to the main Incident Management menu. The command to run this option is "pmm".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F4 - Document Report by: Runs the document by category report using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "drc".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F5 - Excessive Reassignment: Runs the excessive reassignment report using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "err".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F6 - Open Document Report: Runs the open document report using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "odr".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F7 - Shift Change Report: Runs the shift Change report using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "scr".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F8 - Incident Report-Component: Runs the document summary by component using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "prcomp".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F9 - Incident Report-Vendor: Runs the document summary by vendor using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "prvend".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F10 - Incident Report-Assignment: Runs the document summary by assignment group using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "prassg".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F11 - Incident Report-Location: Runs the document summary by location using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "prloc".</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:05</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:13</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
