<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=&quot;link&quot; and term=&quot;Link overview&quot; and format.name=&quot;link&quot; and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="link - Link overview - link - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name type="string">link</file.name>
    <format.name type="string">link</format.name>
    <term type="string">Link overview</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">This form displays an overview of the link record.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Since this is a general view, it does not display the individual links in their entirety. All fields in the individual link arrays are display only. You cannot update it from this screen.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Press Enter to redisplay the screen.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">OPTION KEYS</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F1 (Add Link): Adds a new link record. Use this key to add the link record after entering all desired information. This key does not display for an existing link.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F2 (Update Link): Updates an existing link record. Use this key to save any changes you make to a link record. Service Manager only displays this key for existing links. If you have changed or added a link detail line using the F5 or F6 keys, you must still update the record to save the changes.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F3 (End): Returns you to the previous link maintenance screen, without updating the link record.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F4 (Delete Link): Deletes the link record. Service Manager only displays this key for existing links.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F5 (New Line): Opens a blank form where you may add a new individual link at the bottom of the arrays. The add line key adds a new line to the arrays; it does not update the record.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F6 (Edit Line): Opens a form for the individual link for editing. Before selecting this option, put your cursor on the source field array at the line you want to view. Even when updating the line, the arrays are updated, not the record.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F8 (Copy/Rename): Opens the link.copy screen, where you may rename or copy the link record.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F10 (Next): Takes you to the next link record in the list, without updating. Service Manager only displays this key when you have selected the link record from a search list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F11 (Previous): Takes you to the prior link record in the list, without updating. Service Manager only displays this key when you have selected the link record from a search list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F12 (Menu): Exits the link maintenance utility without updating.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:08</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:17</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
