<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;introrad&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="introrad -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">introrad</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">Rapid Application Development (RAD) enables you to build reliable applications quickly and easily.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">After designing an application, build it with Rapid Application Development (RAD).</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">1. Set up all tables and forms using Forms Designer and the Database Dictionary utility.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">2. Set up the Application Encyclopedia record. This operation automatically builds a default parameter form for the application. You can modify the parameter form later, if necessary.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Specify the name of the application, the application's title, and brief comments that define the application's function. The Application Encyclopedia creates the parameter form and displays the Encyclopedia record after you press F1 or click Create Application.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">3. Modify the parameter from the Encyclopedia record, press F2 or click Edit Application and then press Enter.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Service Manager displays the parameter form with the application and label fields filled in.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Fill in the comments field, and the normal and error fields.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Type "$normal" in the field called normal.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Type "$error" in the field called error.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Type parameter names (beginning with dollar signs ($)) in all the parameter fields if you have added any, and press Enter.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">4. Put in the command panels.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Indicate the name of the next command panel in the Application field and press F 4 or click Application.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Fill in the command panel.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Label is a required field.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Press Enter.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Rapid Application Development (RAD) fills in the label from the previous panel, provided it is not a duplicate of an existing label within the application and it is not a variable name.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Add the rest of the panels.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When finished, press F5 or click Compile.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If there are obvious errors, Service Manager displays error messages. Correct these errors and recompile.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">5. Test the application.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- From the Encyclopedia record, press F9 or click Test Application.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Fill in the parameter names and values to pass the application (if any) and then run it by pressing Enter.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- When completed, press F 3 or click End to return to the Application Encyclopedia.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Note: You can only enter character-valued parameters when using F9 for testing. To test applications with non-character-valued parameters, build a test application that calls the new application using the application's parameter form.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:07</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:15</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
