<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;Keys&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="Keys -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">Keys</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">You can use queries to search on any field or combination of fields in a table.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">The search is significantly faster if the fields are keys. All sort sequences must be keys, either simple or concatenated.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">When you create a table from a form using the (create file) function, Service Manager automatically creates a unique key from the first input field on your form. You must set up additional keys manually, while editing the dbdict. When deciding the Type designation for a key, give the purpose of the key careful consideration.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">A unique field must contain unique data; there may be no two records in the table containing the same data in this field. Be careful of this when changing an existing key to unique, for a table that already contains data.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">The placement and order of keys is crucial for speed of Query-by-Example (QBE) searches.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If the type's function is not necessary, do not use it. For example, if the key is for sorting, it is not necessary to define its type as unique. No nulls, no duplicates or nulls&amp;duplicates suffice, and do not conflict with any intended use of the field.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When storing a key that includes a structure name (such as header,number) the query must select or sort using the structure name also.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:06</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:13</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
