<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;User utilities menu&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="User utilities menu -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">User utilities menu</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">This is the main menu for all user utilities.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">From this menu, you may access the various user utilities. The menu only displays utilities allowed by your individual capabilities.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">OPTIONS</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F1 - Receive Mail: Enables you to read mail. The command to run this option is "rmail".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F2 - Send Mail: Enables you to send mail to other users. The command to run this option is "smail".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F3 - MAIN MENU: Returns you to the main menu. The command to run this option is "main".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F4 - Database Dictionary: Calls the Database Dictionary utility. The command to run this option is "dbdict".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F5 - Display System Status: Enables you to see the status of all users (including background schedulers) in Service Manager. The command to run this option is "status".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F6 - View/Sched Spooled Rpts: Enables you to view or schedule reports in the spool table.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F7 - Maintain Schedule Queue: Enables you to see the scheduled background jobs using Database Manager. The command to run this option is "schedule".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F8 - Help Maintenance: Enables you to maintain online help records using Database Manager. The command to run this option is "help".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F9 - Format Contrl Maint.: Enables you to maintain Format Control records. The command to run this option is "fc".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F10 - Set Operator Password: Enables you to add or change user's password. This does not affect any external passwords. The command to run this option is "password".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F11 - Sched Backgrnd Mail Check: Enables you to schedule a background mail check. This check notifies all users with active server connections if they have mail every 10 minutes, or whatever interval you set. The command to run this option is "schmail".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F12 - More User Utilities: Sends you to the second user utilities menu. The command to run this option is "moreutil".</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:06</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:14</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
