<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;introdatabase&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="introdatabase -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">introdatabase</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">The Service Manager Database Manager is a multi-user, database management system with network-like links.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">The DBMS is efficient because it uses a balanced, compressed B-tree, and key and data compression for efficient use of storage. It can hold an unlimited number of fields, records, and tables.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Tables and fields are form-independent and Forms Designer automatically generates their specifications with default data validation. Full data validation and security capabilities are available in the Database Dictionary utility.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Table and record locking functions occur automatically with a database access command.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">You can specify data relationships with either traditional, relational joins or user-defined links.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">The Database Manager utility supports the following single and multiple record functions:</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">- File Reset</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Index Regeneration</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- List Print</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Record Add</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Record Delete</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Record Display</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Record Link</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Record Load and Unload</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Record Print</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">- Record Update</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">There is no practical limit to the number of records that you can add or access using the Database Manager.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">For record retrieval, Database Manager uses either the Query-By-Example (QBE) method, or the Standard Query Language (SQL) method, whichever is more efficient. It selects the method at the time of the query.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">The Database Manager provides three major groups of option keys. Each group is available depending upon the level of processing the user has. Service Manager displays the first group of options on the initial form. These options support single record maintenance or address the table as a single entity.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Service Manager displays the second group of options when it displays a specific record after the user entered a search argument at the initial form. These options manipulate single records.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Service Manager displays the third group of option if it retrieves more than one record. These options perform mass functions on all records in the search list.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:07</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:14</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
