<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;introincident&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="introincident -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">introincident</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">Incident Management enables you to track an Incident from the time it is first reported to the network control center help desk until it is finally resolved and closed.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">This process involves some or all of the following stages:</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">1. Opening an Incident when it is first reported.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string">2. Updating an Incident when additional information is available.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string">3. Closing an Incident when it is resolved.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string">4. Reopening an Incident if it is reactivated.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">A typical network control center has a System/Software group, an Applications group, an Operations group, and a Communications group.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Although network environments vary from center to center, they all have one thing in common: Incident Management. Incident Management maintains network efficiency, user support, and control over recurring and unresolved Incidents. Service Manager permits you to tailor its user interface to fit your network requirements. Its function is data gathering, retrieval, and reporting.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Incidents are categorized by type because each Incident Type or category requires different information for the open, update, and close processes. For example, a terminal Incident requires different information than an application Incident. The definitions of Incident screen forms are based on these categories.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When an Incident opens, groups are assigned the responsibility of tracking specific Incidents to ensure their swift resolution. The last step is to define the default alert intervals (days or hours/minutes), based on category.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">A default alert interval is the time allowed for the next Incident action. Unless you set a specific alert interval or time period, Service Manager uses the default. When the alert interval passes, Service Manager sends a message notifying management and/or assignment groups that Incident resolution deadlines have not been met. Service Manager then updates the Incident stating the status and who it notified.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">To access the Incident Management Menu, follow these steps:</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">1. From the Main Menu, press the option key for the Incident Management Menu, or from any menu, specify the appropriate command string on the command line and press Enter.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">2. Service Manager displays the Incident Management Menu.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">In order to use Service Manager Incident Management effectively, set up all the pertinent database tables first. This allows Service Manager to fill in information automatically, thus increasing productivity and decreasing data entry efforts.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:07</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:15</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
