<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;Change approvals&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="Change approvals -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">Change approvals</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">Before work can start on a change, the appropriate approval group must approve it.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">The change approval function enables members of the approval group to review the change and Approve or Disapprove it.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Change Approvals do not add new pages to the Change request. They modify the approval status on the last page.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">To select a Change request to be approved or disapproved, either press F7 (Authorize) from a blank Change Header screen to select from a search list, or press F7 (Authorize) from a previously selected change.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Service Manager checks the Approval Table against the current operator login ID to verify your authority to Approve or Disapprove the change.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Once a record is selected for authorization, press either F1 (Approve) or F2 (Disapprove), and the approval status for the id's approval group is modified accordingly.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Once one user from each approval group has either approved or disapproved the Change request, Service Manager modifies the approval status for the Change request accordingly.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Once a Change has a status of Approved, you cannot add or cancel tasks until an authorized approver changes the status back to Pending.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">To undo an approval, press F8 (Unauthorize) from an already approved Change request. This automatically changes the approval status back to Pending.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:05</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:12</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
