<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=NULL and file.name=NULL and term=&quot;Incident Management menu&quot; and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="Incident Management menu -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <file.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term type="string">Incident Management menu</term>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">This is the main menu for the Incident Management module.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">From this menu, you may access the various items contained within Incident Management.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Service Manager only displays the keys that your individual capabilities allow.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">OPTIONS</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F1 - Document Management: Calls the Incident Management driver application. Depending on your individual capabilities, it enables you to browse, open, update, close, and print Incident records. The command to run this option is "dm".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F2 - Assignment Group File: Calls the Incident assignment group table using Database Manager. It enables you to browse and maintain Incident assignment groups. The command to run this option is "assign".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F3 - MAIN MENU: Returns you to the main menu. The command to run this option is "main".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F4 - Category File: Calls the Incident category table using Database Manager. It enables you to browse and maintain Incident categories. The command to run this option is "category". Use the F10 (Create New Category) key when creating new categories requiring new forms.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F5 - Resolution File: Calls the Incident resolution table using Database Manager. It enables you to browse and maintain standard resolutions. The command to run this option is "resol".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F6 - Doc Mgmt Analysis Reports: Sends you to the Incident Analysis Reporting menu. The command to run this option is "dmrpts".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F7 - Assignment Group Listing: Runs the Incident assignment group listing using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "asgnlist".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F8 - Category Listing: Runs the Incident category listing using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "catlist".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F9 - Resolution Code Listing: Runs the standard Incident resolution listing using the report exerciser. The command to run this option is "reslist".</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">F10 - Create New Category: Calls the create Incident category application.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Use this key when creating categories requiring new forms. The command to run this option is "createcat".</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/29/06 23:34:05</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">1</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">06/03/15 17:52:22</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
