<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;unique.b&quot; and file.name=&quot;auditspecs&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="unique.b - auditspecs -  -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">unique.b</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">auditspecs</file.name>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">Service Manager uses this key field to parallel data records in the audit table with data records in the source table.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Under most circumstances, the fields you specify for Unique A thru D are the fields you define as unique keys in the dbdict.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">You can use No Nulls or No Dups key fields for Unique A through D, if Unique key fields are not available. However, if you use No Nulls keys, Audit Records can be related to different source records. In that case, it is difficult (if not impossible) to determine the source record to which the Audit Records are related.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Do not use Nulls&amp;Duplicates keys to define Unique A thru D because if the field(s) in the key are NULL, then Audit Records could be created that do not relate to any record in the Source Table.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Service Manager does not require you to define Unique A through D as keys in the Source Table. However, you must ensure that the non-key field(s) exist and are unique in order to avoid the potential problems.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Note: When defining Audit Specifications for the Incident and Change Management tables, the only field that you must parallel is Number. It is not necessary to parallel the Last or Page fields.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:35:20</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:49:46</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
