<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;files&quot; and file.name=&quot;validity&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="files - validity -  -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">files</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">validity</file.name>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">The names of the tables and forms to which this field validation applies.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">Normal Validity table processing validates all fields associated with the table of the data record it is validating; however, there are circumstances when only the fields defined to a particular form need to be validated and the remainder of the fields associated with that table should be ignored.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When this occurs, you can define that form name here to change validity processing to validate only the fields associated with that form. This is done by passing the name of the form to the validation routine.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">The validity validation routine requires a minimum of one definition for this field. Each value must be a valid table or form name.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">The validation routine searches the dbdict table first. If an entry is not in dbdict, the routine searches the format table.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If the entry is not a valid form name, a record list of valid names is displayed. From this list, you can invoke a search against the format table to select a valid form name.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Note: If you select a form, it must be associated with a valid file and the Field Name must exist in that file.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If the form is not associated with a table, you are prompted to select one from a list of valid tables.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:34:37</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:48:51</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
