<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;legacy.suspend&quot; and file.name=&quot;slamodulecontrol&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="legacy.suspend - slamodulecontrol -  -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">legacy.suspend</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">slamodulecontrol</file.name>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">If selected (set to true), Service Manager measures responsiveness based on the response Service Level Targets (SLTs) of the record by using the legacy method, which does not consider the state progression order of the record.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">If cleared (set to false), Service Manager uses another method for responsiveness measurement, which takes the state progression order of the record into account.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">Suppose the following SLT is defined for Incident records:</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Initial state: Open</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Final State: Work In Progress</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">Suspend processing for these states: Pending Vendor, and Pending Change</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">The response state progression order in the slamodulecontrol definition for Incident is as follows: Open, Pending Vendor, Work In Progress, Pending Change, Resolved, and Closed</detail>
      <detail sctype="string">When this option is selected, once an incident record moves to a suspending state, the running SLT will be suspended directly without checking its order in the response states list or phase list. For example,  when the record moves to either the Pending Vendor  state (which is before the final state) or the Pending Change state (which is after the final state), the running SLT is suspended.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">When this option is not selected, when the record moves to the Pending Vendor  state (which is before the final state), the running SLT is suspended; however, when the record moves to the Pending Change state (which is after the final state), the running SLT is achieved.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">11/12/14 03:34:41</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">dengxin</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">14</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">qiqingsong</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">11/12/14 03:34:41</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
