<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;source.fields&quot; and file.name=&quot;link&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="source.fields - link -  -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">source.fields</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">link</file.name>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">The source fields on the current form for individual links.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">Press F6-Edit Line with the cursor on the source field to edit the query, QBE form or the individual fields to fill.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">When doing a find or fill, Service Manager selects the individual links based on the field the cursor is on matching one or more of these fields.</brief>
      <brief sctype="string"/>
      <brief sctype="string">When you click fill, Service Manager fills the like-named fields from the target table into the source table, unless the individual fields to fill array is complete for the line, in which case only the fields specified are filled.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">These are the names of the input field on the form that enables the user to begin the Posting process.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">You can define the same input field multiple times on the Link record. If more than one field in the list matches the source input field, the Posting process is completed for all fields in the list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Use existing input fields or define special input fields to invoke Posting to a particular table. For example, add the input fields called post.to.problem and post.to.change. Each of these input fields would then be defined to the Posting link record. This enables the user to place the cursor on either field and invoke the Posting process defined for that input field.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Consider using special input fields for the Posting process if you define a Posting link on the same form used for find/fill and if the same source input field defines the unique target record used for find, fill and Posting. This is because the fields that are filled from a target table will probably not be the same fields that are Posted to a target table.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">This is an array (type 8) of characters (type 2).</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:35:13</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:49:37</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
