<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<recordset table="help">
  <record id="field.name=&quot;repeat.type&quot; and file.name=&quot;patcotask&quot; and term=NULL and format.name=NULL and syslanguage=&quot;en&quot;" recordid="repeat.type - patcotask -  -  - en">
    <topic NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <field.name type="string">repeat.type</field.name>
    <file.name type="string">patcotask</file.name>
    <format.name NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <term NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <keywords NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <keywords NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </keywords>
    <brief sctype="array">
      <brief sctype="string">The type of repeat interval.</brief>
    </brief>
    <detail sctype="array">
      <detail sctype="string">OPTIONS</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Regularly: If selected (set to true), indicates a regular repeat interval. If you select this option, you must also choose the date and time for the first occurrence in the Every field.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Weekly: If selected (set to true), indicates a Weekly repeat interval.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If you select this option, you must also select the day of the week from the Every drop-down list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Monthly: (Date in the month): If selected (set to true), indicates a monthly repeat interval. If you select this option, you must select a date from the Every drop-down list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Monthly: (Week and day of the month)</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">If you select this option, you must also select a week of the month from the Every drop-down list and then select a day of the week from the second drop-down list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Annually: (Date in the year) If selected (set to true), indicates an Annual repeat interval. If you select this option, you must also select the sequential day of the year from the Every drop-down list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Annually: (Month and day of the year) If selected (set to true), indicates an Annual repeat interval. If you select this option, you must also select a month from the Every drop-down list, and select a date from the second drop-down list.</detail>
      <detail sctype="string"/>
      <detail sctype="string">Arbitrary Schedule: If selected (set to true), indicates specific dates. If you select this option, you must also click a row in the Recurrence Schedule table and choose a date and time. Repeat this step for each scheduled occurrence.</detail>
    </detail>
    <record.number NullValue="1" type="decimal"/>
    <customer.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <copy.id NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <old.module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <update.time type="dateTime">06/30/06 05:35:06</update.time>
    <required NullValue="1" type="boolean"/>
    <owner NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    <module NullValue="1" sctype="array">
      <module NullValue="1" type="string"/>
    </module>
    <operator type="string">falcon</operator>
    <syslanguage type="string">en</syslanguage>
    <sysmodcount type="decimal">0</sysmodcount>
    <sysmoduser type="string">falcon</sysmoduser>
    <sysmodtime type="dateTime">05/08/07 07:49:29</sysmodtime>
    <pending.review type="boolean">false</pending.review>
  </record>
</recordset>
